Guide to the Class of 1929, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, Records
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
Class of 1929, Sheffield Scientific School, Yale University, records
1928-1993
RU 952
Yale University. Department of Manuscripts and Archives
2
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, news clippings, photographs and sound recordings documenting the Yale Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1929 and its reunions.
Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School. Class of 1929
General note
Forms part of Yale Record Group 10-B (YRG 10-B), Records of Sheffield Scientific School classes.
Immediate Source of Acquisition
The records were donated by Howard Gambrill, 2004; family of Watson F. Kinney, 2008.
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the materials is restricted. See Collection Contents for details.
Scope and Contents
The records consist of correspondence, subject files, news clippings, photographs and sound recordings documenting the Yale Sheffield Scientific School Class of 1929 and its reunions.
Arrangement
The records are arranged by accession.
Class reunions; Universities and colleges -- Alumni and alumnae; Photographs; Yale University -- Alumni and alumnae; Yale University. Sheffield Scientific School. Class of 1929
- Photographs, newsclipping, and ephemera of Howard Gambrill (1929S), documenting Yale, circa 1928-1993; Accession 2004-A-176
  - 50th Reunion [binder], 1978-1979 (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Correspondence
    - Program, news
    - Registration, rooms
    - Hotel, Morey's
    - Yale Bowl
    - Tours: Yale Art Gallery, Center for British Art, University libraries
    - Friday Space Talk
    - Class dinner, 1979 May 25
    - Memorial service
    - Lobster bake and finale, 1979 May 27
    - Memos, correspondence
  - 50th Reunion costs, 1978-1980 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - 50th Reunion publications, 1979 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Princeton Alumni Weekly clipping, 1979 July 16 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Yale '29 since 50th Reunion [snapshots, reunion button, notes for dinner talk], Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Yale 55th Reunion, 1982-1984 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Memberships: Yale Club of Boston, 1956-1985 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - President Brewster - Yale, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Yale: Timothy Dwight Fellows 1968-1983; medalists, 1969-1983 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Special Yale Personal [clippings, photos, certificates, etc.], 1960-1994 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Yale [correspondence, memos], 1980-1984 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Yale '29: Class Secreatary, 1974-1981 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Yale '29: Correspondence, P.K. Fodder, treasurer, 1974-1978 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Yale '29: Dinners and lunches, New Haven, 1975-1976 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Photographs, 1972-1974 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Yale '29: Miscellaneous correspondence with alumni offices, 1979-1993 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Yale '29 Dinners: Washington, D.C., 1975 January 24-25 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Miscellaneous [mainly 40th Reunion, including Yale Medal citation], 1969-1993 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - Audiotapes
    - Kandy (2nd side), Yale Glee, Comm [?], 1962? June 10-11 (Box 1, Folder 19)
    - Base and Chimes and Class Day, 1962 June 10
    - Kandy 2 (N.G.), Chimes, Benediction - Davenport, 1962 June 11
  - Photographs, 1929, 1979, undated (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Memorabilia of Watson F. Kinney, Class of1929S, 1909-2004; Accession 2008-A-131
  - Athletics - Gilmore Kinney, undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Button, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Class of 1929 tenth year album, 1939 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Clippings and ephemera, 1926-1997 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Commencement program, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence and alumni information, 1933-2004 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Drawing of Harkness Tower, undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Graduation exercises, 1929 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Patches and armband, 1909, 1701 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Photographs, 1925-1929 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Photographs, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Photographs, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Photographs, circa 1989 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Photographs, undated (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Postcards, 1954 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Slides - 30th Reunion, 1959 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - Slides - 35th Reunion, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - The Yale Standard, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 18)